Welcome to the apocalypse.
The Lost Future is a adventure, science fiction, tv
movie film directed by Mikael Salomon.
A group of post-apocalyptic survivors, struggle to survive in a world where jungles and
forests and primeval wetlands and deserts have obliterated civilization.
They staunchly face genetically mutating beasts and mysterious diseases in an
attempt to re-establish the human race as masters of Earth.
Amal, played by Sean Bean.
Dorel, played by Annabelle Wallis.
Savan, played by Corey Sevier.
Miru, played by Eleanor Tomlinson.
Gagen, played by Jonathan Pienaar.
Giselle, played by Hannah Tointon.
The Lost Future is a 2010 South African-German post-apocalyptic film from
Syfy, directed by Mikael Salomon and written by Jonas Bauer.
The film stars Sean Bean, Corey Sevier and Sam Claflin.
It was released on DVD on 27 September 2011.
The film explores themes of post-apocalyptic future, giant
monster, distant future, jungle, virus.
The tone is thought_provoking.